# Andrés Bastidas Fierro Systems & Computer Engineer

andbastidasfierro@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/andbastidasfierro





+54 9 11 64 265626







@andbastf

be.net/andbastf



#### About Me

I was born in Tulcán, Ecuador and have been living in Buenos Aires, Argentina for 5 years, working in my own fintech company. I'm 28 years old and since young I've been passionate about visual arts mainly thanks to a big influence from my mother side, her being a graphic designer, and her father being a poet. During my youth I was self-taught of digital design tools, interfaces, modeling and animation so when the time to chose an university degree came I decided to follow a more technical branch in order to complement all the design bases already learned.

A huge fan of videogames, during my free time I have been building experiments of digital experiences among which I include virtual and augmented reality, considering them as avante-garde technologies and eventually necessary in society, requiring their own set of interactions, similar to our current contact with a computer, but resembling reality and how we approach to it.

#### Education

Pontificia Universidad Católica del Ecuador

ago2010 - dic2016

**System & Computer Engineering** 

### Software









**Engines** 



Ps



Adobe Suite

**Atlassian** 

## Experience

Qienna Wealth Management Inc

jul 2021 - present

**Product Manager** 

nov2020 - jul2021

**UX/UI Leader** 

jan2016 - nov2020

Front/UX/UI Developer

Halliburton - Oilfield Services jun 2014 - jan 2015

**Content Manager** 

atiko7 - Digital Solutions sep2013 - mar2014

## Languages













### Awards

youtube.com/watch?v=-x5fG51wNPk

**1st National Place** 

Les 24h de l'innovation

twitter.com/CiudadYachay/status/738796781723607040

1er Place

Retos Yachay 2015 "enerMe"